<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>NAUSEATING PAROXYSMS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The contagion borne by the Death Guard and their 
attendant swarms of winged vermin triggers bouts of 
sickness and convulsion in those they encounter.</lore>
    <when>Start of the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Death Guard Infantry  unit from your 
army that is within Engagement Range of one or 
more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit within Engagement 
Range of your unit. That unit must take a 
Battle‑shock test, subtracting 1 from the result.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>VERMIN CLOUD</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The storm of insectile contagion sweeps forward, 
dragging the Death Guard in its wake. None will 
escape the Plague God’s embrace.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Death Guard Infantry  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in this unit makes a Pile‑in or Consolidation 
move, it can move up to 6&quot; instead of up to 3&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>EYE OF THE SWARM</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The vermin swarms intensify as the Death Guard 
close in upon the enemy. As their foes clutch and 
tear their crawling skin, pitiless Plague Marines 
unleash volleys of point‑blank fire into their 
tormented foes.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Death Guard Infantry  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, ranged weapons 
equipped by models in your unit (excluding Blast 
weapons) have the [PISTOL]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DRONING HORROR</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Clouds of droning daemon flies sweep across the 
battlefield to envelop the enemies of the Death 
Guard. As their victims claw and scratch at the 
seething swarms, Mortarion’s sons pick off their 
targets at leisure.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Death Guard Infantry  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes a ranged attack, re‑roll a 
Hit roll of 1. If that attack targets a unit within half 
range, you can re‑roll the Hit roll instead.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ENERVATING ONSLAUGHT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Swathed in a buzzing cloak of pathogenic decay, 
Nurgle’s chosen crash into the foe, disease dealing 
death as surely as fist, maul and blade.</lore>
    <when>Your Charge phase, just after a Death Guard 
Infantry  unit from your army makes a Charge move.</when>
    <target>That Death Guard Infantry unit.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit within Engagement 
Range of your unit (excluding Monsters  and 
Vehicles ). Roll one D6 for each model in your 
unit that is within Engagement Range of that unit, 
adding 1 to the result if that model is not a Cultist  or 
Poxwalker  model: for each 5+, the selected enemy 
unit suffers 1 mortal wound (to a maximum of 6 
mortal wounds).</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MYPHITIC INVIGORATION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FLYBLOWN HOST</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Daemon flies are drawn to and invigorated by the 
foul miasmas surrounding Myphitic Blight‑haulers. 
In the vicinity of these malodorous constructs, the 
swarms gather in densities great enough to form a 
living barrier to the foe’s attacks.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One Death Guard Infantry  unit from 
your army that is within 6&quot; of one or more friendly 
Myphitic Blight‑hauler units and that was 
selected as the target of one or more of the attacking 
unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an 
attack targets your unit, if the Strength characteristic 
of that attack is greater than the Toughness 
characteristic of this unit, subtract 1 from the 
Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
