<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MACHINE WRATH</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>EPIC DEED STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>In a last act of vengeance, the doomed crew of this 
burning transport drive into the midst of the enemy.</lore>
    <when>Any phase, just after a Heavy Transport  unit 
from your army is destroyed.</when>
    <target>That Heavy Transport  unit. You can use 
this Stratagem on that unit even though it was 
just destroyed.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal or Fall Back 
move before you roll for its Deadly Demise ability, and 
before any embarked units perform an Emergency 
Disembarkation. When making this move, your 
unit can move through enemy models (excluding 
Monsters  and Vehicles ) and can move within 
Engagement Range of such models, but cannot end 
that move within Engagement Range of them, and 
any Desperate Escape test is automatically passed.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOUR OF CONTEMPT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The belligerence of the Adeptus Astartes, combined 
with their transhuman physiology, makes them 
unyielding foes to face.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time 
an attack targets your unit, worsen the Armour 
Penetration characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>RAPID EMBARKATION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>WARGEAR STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>With steely discipline, Space Marine battle‑brothers 
mount up swiftly, even as the enemy closes in.</lore>
    <when>End of the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  Infantry  unit from 
your army that is not within Engagement Range of 
one or more enemy units, and one friendly Heavy 
Transport  it is able to embark within.</target>
    <effect>If your Adeptus Astartes Infantry  unit 
is wholly within 6&quot; of that Heavy Transport , it can 
embark within it.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>CERAMITE SLEDGEHAMMER</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The mightiest Space Marine transports are 
unstoppable on the advance.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Transport  unit 
from your army that has not been selected to move 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time your 
unit makes a Normal or Advance move, it can move 
horizontally through terrain features. In addition, if 
your unit is a Heavy Transport , when making this 
move, your unit can move through enemy models 
(excluding Monsters  and Vehicles ) and can 
move within Engagement Range of such models, 
but cannot end that move within Engagement 
Range of them, and any Desperate Escape test is 
automatically passed.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ADVANCED DEPLOYMENT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Coaxing the utmost from roaring engines, transport 
crews strive to deploy their passengers as close as 
possible to their assigned objectives.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Transport  unit 
from your army that has not been selected to move 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, units can 
disembark from your Transport  after it has 
Advanced. Units that do so count as having made a 
Normal move this phase, and cannot declare a charge 
in the same turn (unless your Transport  has the 
Assault Ramp ability), but can otherwise act normally.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>PURGATION DOCTRINE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ARMOURED SPEARTIP</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Emerging from their transports, Space Marine 
infantry ruthlessly clear enemy positions.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack, add 1 to the 
Hit roll (if your unit disembarked from a Heavy 
Transport  this turn, add 1 to the Wound roll as well).</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
