<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>CODEX DISCIPLINE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Holding to the teachings of the Codex Astartes, these 
warriors unleash disciplined volleys of firepower.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot or fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack that targets 
an enemy unit, re‑roll a Hit roll of 1. If that target is 
auspex scanned, re‑roll a Wound roll of 1 as well.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>GUIDED DISRUPTION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Employing auspex data to reveal weak points in the 
foe’s formation, the Space Marines exploit these to 
sow confusion and suppress their targets.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase, just 
after an Adeptus Astartes Battleline  unit from 
your army has finished making its attacks.</when>
    <target>That Adeptus Astartes Battleline  unit.</target>
    <effect>When an enemy unit is auspex scanned as 
a result of those attacks this turn, if that enemy unit 
does not have the Monster  or Vehicle  keywords, 
until the start of your next turn, it is pinned. While 
a unit is pinned, subtract 2 from that unit’s Move 
characteristic and subtract 2 from Charge rolls made 
for that unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>LIGHT OF VENGEANCE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>With their frailties exposed by the harsh glare of 
auspex analysis, the foe are easy prey for the Space 
Marine’  vengeful onslaught.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot or fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Select the [LETHAL HITS]  or 
[SUSTAINED HITS 1]  ability. Until the end of the phase, 
weapons equipped by models in your unit have that 
ability while targeting an auspex scanned unit or if 
the bearer has the Battleline  keyword.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SHOCK BOMBARDMENT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>An auspex‑guided hail of shock charges blinds the 
foe’s targeting systems and skews their aim.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase, just 
after an Adeptus Astartes Battleline  unit from 
your army finished making its attacks.</when>
    <target>That Adeptus Astartes Battleline  unit.</target>
    <effect>When an enemy unit is auspex scanned 
as a result of those attacks this turn, until the start 
of your next turn, it is suppressed. While a unit is 
suppressed, each time a model in that unit makes an 
attack, subtract 1 from the Hit roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ANGELS DEFIANT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>All too aware of their vital role in holding the foe at 
bay, these battle‑brothers refuse to yield to even the 
most grievous of wounds.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Battleline  unit 
from your army that was selected as the target of 
one or more of the attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an 
attack targets your unit, if the Strength characteristic 
of that attack is greater than the Toughness 
characteristic of your unit, subtract 1 from the 
Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>HERESY UNDONE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BASTION TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Tactical scans and cogitator analysis have revealed 
the enemy’s debase schemes, rendering their 
movements easier to anticipate and counter.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or your Charge phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit (excluding 
Battleline  units) from your army.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, your unit is 
eligible to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in 
which it Advanced or Fell Back. If it does, every target 
of that charge and every target of those attacks must 
be an auspex scanned unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
