<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOUR OF CONTEMPT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The belligerence of the Adeptus Astartes combined 
with their post‑human physiology makes them 
unyielding foes to face.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an attack 
targets your unit, worsen the Armour Penetration 
characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>TACTICAL FORESIGHT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>EPIC DEED STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>With the enemy’s countermeasures and responses 
predicted and allowed for in advance, the Ultramarines 
can weather their most ferocious attacks.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an 
attack targets your unit, if the Strength characteristic 
of that attack is greater than or equal to the Toughness 
characteristic of that unit, subtract 1 from the 
Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>COURAGE AND HONOUR!</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Roaring their famed battle cry, the Ultramarines 
hurl themselves into the fight, striving all the harder 
to prevail beneath the unwavering eye of their 
Chapter Master.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, melee weapons 
equipped by models in your unit have the [LANCE]  
ability. If your unit is under the effects of the Assault 
Doctrine, until the end of the phase, improve the 
Armour Penetration characteristic of such weapons by 
1 as well.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ULTRAMARIAN ADAPTIVITY</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>No Chapter’s warriors know better the breadth – 
theoretical and practical – of the Codex Astartes’ 
teachings, and how these can and should be adapted 
to ensure victory.</lore>
    <when>Your Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Select the Devastator Doctrine, Tactical 
Doctrine or Assault Doctrine. Until the start of your next 
Command phase, that Combat Doctrine is active for 
your unit instead of any other Combat Doctrine that is 
active for your army, even if you have already selected 
that Combat Doctrine this battle.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>EXEMPLARY VIGILANCE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Long have the Ultramarines guarded both Ultramar 
and the wider Imperium. No foe can hide from their 
vengeful gaze or evade the reach of their wrath.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, ranged 
weapons equipped by models in your unit have the 
[IGNORES COVER]  ability. If your unit is under the 
effects of the Devastator Doctrine, until the end of the 
phase, improve the Armour Penetration characteristic 
of such weapons by 1 as well.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>PRACTICAL TACTICS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLADE OF ULTRAMAR</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>After rapidly making a theoretical assessment of the 
foes’ probable next moves, the Ultramarines apply 
practical repositioning to counter them.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just after an 
enemy unit ends a Normal, Advance or Fall Back move.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry  or Adeptus 
Astartes Mounted  unit from your army that is not 
within Engagement Range of one or more enemy units 
and is within 9&quot; of the enemy unit that just ended 
that move.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of up to 
D6&quot;, or a Normal move of up to 6&quot; instead if it is under 
the effects of the Tactical Doctrine.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
