<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOUR OF CONTEMPT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The belligerence of the Adeptus Astartes, combined 
with their transhuman physiology, makes them 
unyielding foes to face.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit  from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time 
an attack targets your unit, worsen the Armour 
Penetration characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>TARGET WEAK POINT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Targeting vulnerable joints or seams between 
armoured plates, Space Marine gunners increase the 
effectiveness of their weapons.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Tank Ace  unit from your army that has 
not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes a ranged attack that 
targets a Monster or Vehicle  unit, improve the 
Armour Penetration characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
    <restrictions>A unit cannot be targeted with this 
and the Kill Shot Stratagem in the same phase.</restrictions>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>KILL SHOT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Space Marines are ruthless in culling weakened foes.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Tank Ace  unit from your army that has 
not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack that targets a 
Monster  or Vehicle  unit, re‑roll a Wound roll of 1. If 
the target unit is below its Starting Strength, you can 
re‑roll the Wound roll instead.</effect>
    <restrictions>A unit cannot be targeted with 
this and the Target Weak Point Stratagem in the 
same phase.</restrictions>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>RAPID GUNNERY</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Advanced targeting systems and the skill of 
transhuman gunners ensure that Space Marine 
tanks keep up a punishing rate of fire, even when 
extracting themselves from a press of enemies.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, your unit is 
eligible to shoot in a turn in which it Fell Back.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>REACTIVE REPOSITIONING</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Reacting swiftly to enemy movements, this tank’s 
crew reposition their vehicle, angling armour or 
taking up an advantageous firing position.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just 
after an enemy unit ends a Normal, Advance or Fall 
Back move.</when>
    <target>One Tank Ace  unit from your army 
(excluding units containing one or more models with 
a Wounds characteristic of 16+) that is within 9&quot; of 
that enemy unit.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of up 
to D6&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MACHINE VENGEANCE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>HEADHUNTER TASK FORCE</type>
    <subtype>EPIC DEED STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Bellicose in the extreme, this vehicle’s machine 
spirit demands immediate vengeance for the hurts 
it has incurred.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has shot.</when>
    <target>One Tank Ace  unit from your army 
(excluding units containing one or more models 
with a Wounds characteristic of 16+) that was 
selected as the target of one or more of the attacking 
unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can shoot as if it were your 
Shooting phase, but must target only that enemy 
unit when doing so, and can only do so if that enemy 
unit is visible and an eligible target.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
