<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SENSORY ASSAULT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Paranoia, confusion and panic are heightened to 
a debilitating degree as the Librarian alters his 
foes’ perceptions.</lore>
    <when>Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Psyker  unit from 
your army.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit that is within 18&quot; of 
and visible to one Psyker  model in your unit. Until 
the start of your next turn, that enemy unit is pinned. 
While a unit is pinned, subtract 2 from that unit’s 
Move characteristic and subtract 2 from Charge rolls 
made for it. In addition, if the Telepathy Discipline is 
active for your army, that enemy unit must take a 
Battle‑shock test, subtracting 1 from the result.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOUR OF CONTEMPT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The belligerence of the Adeptus Astartes combined 
with their post‑human physiology makes them 
unyielding foes to face.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time 
an attack targets your unit, worsen the Armour 
Penetration characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>FIERY SHIELD</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>As the enemy closes in for the kill, the psyker 
manifests his psychic will in a raging inferno 
that obscures imperilled allies and threatens to 
immolate any who come close enough to land a blow 
upon them.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has 
selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry or 
Adeptus Astartes Mounted  unit from your army 
that is within 18&quot; of one or more friendly  Adeptus 
Astartes Psyker models, and that was selected 
as the target of one or more of the attacking 
unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an 
attack targets your unit, subtract 1 from the Hit 
roll, and if the Pyromancy Discipline is active for 
your army, weapons that target your unit have the 
[HAZARDOUS]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>IRON ARM</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>This Librarian lends skull‑shattering weight and 
impact to melee strikes by transmuting flesh into 
unyielding metal.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry  unit from 
your army that is within 18&quot; of one or more Adeptus 
Astartes Psyker models from your army and has 
not been selected to Fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, add 1 to the 
Strength characteristic of melee weapons equipped 
by models in your unit, or add 2 if the Biomancy 
Discipline is active for your army.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ASSAIL</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Using nothing but the power of his mind, a Librarian 
can rip rubble, boulders and other debris from the 
surrounding terrain and hurl them at the foe.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Psyker  unit from 
your army that is eligible to shoot.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit within 18&quot; of and 
visible to one or more Psyker  models in your unit 
(excluding units with the Lone Operative ability), and 
roll six D6, adding 1 to each result if the Telekinesis 
Discipline is active for your army: for each 4+, that 
enemy unit suffers 1 mortal wound.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>PRESCIENT PRECISION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>LIBRARIUS CONCLAVE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Sharing some of his prescience with his 
battle‑brothers, a Librarian can guide their fire.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Psyker unit from 
your army that has not been selected to shoot 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack, that attack has 
the [LETHAL HITS]  ability, and the [IGNORES COVER]  
ability as well if the Divination Discipline is active for 
your army.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
