<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SUPPRESSION STRAFING</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>As the Space Marines storm forward, their gunships 
and fighter craft streak overhead, hammering enemy 
positions with hails of fire to keep the foe pinned.</lore>
    <when>Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit visible to and 
within 18&quot; of your unit. That enemy unit takes a 
Battle‑shock test. When doing so, subtract 1 from 
that test and, if that test is failed, until the start of 
your next turn, that enemy unit is suppressed. While 
a unit is suppressed, each time a model in that unit 
makes an attack, subtract 1 from the Hit roll.</effect>
    <restrictions>You cannot use this Stratagem more 
than once per battle round.</restrictions>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>TACTICAL DECAPITATION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>By rapidly eliminating localised enemy leaders, the 
Space Marines keep the foe off balance and hamper 
organised resistance to their onslaught.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot or fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, weapons 
equipped by models in your unit have the  
[PRECISION] ability and each time a model in your 
unit makes an attack that targets a Character  unit, 
add 1 to the Hit roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SHOCK ONSLAUGHT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The sheer devastating momentum of a Space 
Marine drop assault shatters one enemy battle line 
after another.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that has not been selected to fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes a Pile‑in or Consolidation 
move, it can move up to 6&quot; instead of up to 3&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>AUTO‑SENSE COORDINATION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>By binding the datafeeds from their auto‑senses, 
these battle‑brothers generate triangulated targeting 
solutions for close‑quarters fire spreads.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase or the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to shoot or fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Select the [LETHAL HITS]  or 
[SUSTAINED HITS 1]  ability. Until the end of the 
phase, weapons equipped by models in your unit 
have this ability in a turn in which they disembarked 
from a Drop Pod  or while targeting an enemy unit 
within 12&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>BLIND SCREEN</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Autolaunchers spit a precogitated spread of blind 
grenades to baffle organic and mechanical targeting.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit (excluding 
Titanic  units) from your army that was selected 
as the target of one or more of the attacking unit’s 
attacks and one friendly Adeptus Astartes Smoke 
Vehicle  or Drop Pod  unit within 9&quot; of it.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, models in your 
units have the Stealth ability and each time a ranged 
attack targets one of your units, models in that unit 
have the Benefit of Cover against that attack.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ONWARD FOR THE EMPEROR</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>ORBITAL ASSAULT FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>There is always another battle to be fought, and the 
Space Marines waste no time in fighting it.</lore>
    <when>End of your opponent’s Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry  unit from 
your army that was not set up on the battlefield 
this turn and one friendly Transport  it is able to 
embark within.</target>
    <effect>If your Adeptus Astartes  unit is wholly 
within 6&quot; of that Transport , it can embark within it.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
