<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>CRUSADING CONQUERORS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The sheer will of these battle‑brothers to reclaim the 
sacred Five Hundred Worlds is overwhelming.</lore>
    <when>End of the Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Until the start of the next Command phase, 
add 1 to the Objective Control characteristic of 
models in your unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>FURIOUS DEDICATION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Cold fury of purpose drives the charge of the Space 
Marines, their absolute dedication to their cause 
lending them ferocious speed and strength.</lore>
    <when>Your Charge phase or the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that has not declared a charge or been selected to 
fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, add 2 to Charge 
rolls made for your unit and add 1 to the Attacks 
characteristic of melee weapons equipped by 
models in your unit.</effect>
    <restrictions>You cannot use this Stratagem more 
than once per turn.</restrictions>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>FIGHT TO THE END</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Those who have sworn an oath to see Ultramar 
reclaimed will not yield a single yard of its territories 
once they have seized and secured them.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has 
selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit is destroyed, if that model has not 
fought this phase, roll one D6: on a 4+, do not remove 
the destroyed model from play; it can fight after the 
attacking unit has finished making its attacks, and is 
then removed from play.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SCIONS OF GUILLIMAN</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The gene‑sons of Roboute Guilliman are masters 
of his tenets, regardless of which Chapter they 
hail from.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase, just after an Adeptus 
Astartes unit from your army ends a Fall Back move.</when>
    <target>That Adeptus Astartes unit.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, your unit is eligible 
to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in which it 
Fell Back.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ULTRAMARIAN DESTINY</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>All those Space Marines fighting to defend or to 
expand the Ultramarines stellar realm trust that their 
conquest – though it must be hard fought for – is 
nothing short of ordained by the Primarch’s will.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Select one objective marker you control that 
your unit is within range of. That objective marker 
remains under your control until your opponent’s 
Level of Control over that objective marker is greater 
than yours at the end of a phase.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MARCHING EVER ON</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>RECLAMATION FORCE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The road to the complete rebuilding of the Five 
Hundred Worlds will be a long and gruelling one, and 
those who fight their way along it cannot pause in 
their advance for even a moment.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just after 
an enemy unit Falls Back.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was within Engagement Range of that enemy 
unit at the start of the phase.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of up 
to D6&quot;+1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
