<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOUR OF CONTEMPT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The belligerence of the Adeptus Astartes combined 
with their post‑human physiology makes them 
unyielding foes to face.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase or the 
Fight phase, just after an enemy unit has selected 
its targets.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army 
that was selected as the target of one or more of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an attack 
targets your unit, worsen the Armour Penetration 
characteristic of that attack by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>LAY LOW THE TYRANTS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>In a storm of blade thrusts and bludgeoning strikes, 
enemy champions and commanders are laid low, 
leaving their troops in leaderless disarray.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  Infantry  unit 
from your army that has not been selected to fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, melee weapons 
equipped by models in your unit have the 
[PRECISION]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>FEINT AND THRUST</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Retreating from the fight, these warriors lure their 
enemies on before swiftly turning the tables and 
hurling themselves into their now overextended foe.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes  unit from your army.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, your unit is eligible 
to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in which it Fell 
Back. If it is a Phobos  or Scout Squad  unit, it is also 
eligible to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in which 
it Advanced.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>STUNNING FUSILLADE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>From darkness and obscuring cover, Raven Guard 
battle‑brothers open fire as one, striking their unaware 
targets with precision fire.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry  unit from 
your army that has not been selected to shoot 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a model 
in your unit makes a ranged attack that targets an 
enemy unit that is more than 12&quot; away, improve the 
Ballistic Skill and Armour Penetration characteristics 
of that attack by 1. If one or more enemy models are 
destroyed as a result of those attacks, select one of 
those destroyed models; that destroyed model’s unit 
must take a Battle‑shock test.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>RAPTORIAL VIGILANCE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The Raven Guard are swift to exploit the movements of 
their foes, whether to pursue their prey and complete 
the kill or to make use of an opportunity to fade once 
more from sight.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just after an 
enemy unit ends a Normal, Advance or Fall Back move.</when>
    <target>One Adeptus Astartes Infantry  or Adeptus 
Astartes Mounted  unit from your army that is within 
9&quot; of the enemy unit that just ended that move. You 
cannot target a unit that is within Engagement Range of 
one or more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of 
up to D6&quot;, or up to 6&quot; instead if it is a Phobos  or 
Scout Squad  unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>INTO DARKNESS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SHADOWMARK TALON</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>At the opportune moment, Raven Guard infiltration 
units slip away from battle, only to relocate ready to 
strike the foe again.</lore>
    <when>End of your opponent’s Fight phase.</when>
    <target>Up to two Phobos  and/or Scout Squad  units 
from your army, or one other Adeptus Astartes 
Infantry  unit from your army. You cannot target a 
unit that is within Engagement Range of one or more 
enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Remove those units from the battlefield and 
place them into Strategic Reserves.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
