<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MOUNT UP, LADZ</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>With nothing left to blast or krump, these Orks 
scramble aboard their transport and thunder towards 
the next engagement.</lore>
    <when>End of the Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks Infantry  unit from your army 
that is not within Engagement Range of one or more 
enemy units, and one friendly Transport  it is able to 
embark within.</target>
    <effect>If your Orks Infantry  unit is wholly within 
6&quot; of that Transport , it can embark within it.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MEKANISED BRUTALITY</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>As Orkoid vehicles thunder into battle at high speed, 
hatches and ramps swing open, unleashing eager 
mobs into the thick of the fight.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Battlewagon , Kill Rig  or Hunta Rig 
unit from your army that has not been selected to 
move this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, each time a unit 
disembarks from your unit after your unit makes a 
Normal move, that disembarked unit is still eligible to 
declare a charge this turn.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>RUN ’EM DOWN</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Driving forward in loose formation, Ork vehicles 
smash into the foe, crushing fleeing enemies 
beneath tyres, steel tracks and Squig trotters.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Battlewagon , Kill Rig  or Hunta Rig 
unit from your army that has not been selected to 
move this phase.</target>
    <effect>Select up to two other friendly Orks Vehicle  
or Orks Monster units within 6&quot; of your unit. Until 
the end of the turn, your unit and each unit you 
selected are eligible to declare a charge in a turn in 
which they Advanced.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ARMOURED DUELLISTS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Ork crews delight in engaging enemy vehicles and 
monsters in mobile battles.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks Vehicle  unit from your army that 
has not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time your 
unit makes an attack that targets a Monster  or 
Vehicle  unit, add 1 to the Hit roll and add 1 to the 
Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>IMPERVIOUS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Ramshackle though they may appear, Ork vehicles 
are frighteningly resilient in their construction.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One Battlewagon , Kill Rig  or Hunta Rig  
unit from your army that was selected as the target 
of one or more of the attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time an 
attack targets your unit, if the Strength characteristic 
of that attack is greater than the Toughness 
characteristic of your unit, subtract 1 from the 
Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>YOOZ IN TROUBLE NOW</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>BLITZ BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Spilling from their damaged transport, enraged 
Orkoid infantry mobs surge towards their attackers.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has shot.</when>
    <target>One Battlewagon , Hunta Rig or Kill Rig  
model from your army that was hit by one or more of 
the attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>One Orks Infantry  unit embarked within 
your model can disembark and make a Surge move. 
To do so, roll one D6: models in that unit move a 
number of inches up to this result, but that unit must 
end that move as close as possible to the closest 
enemy unit (excluding Aircraft ). When doing so, 
those models can be moved within Engagement 
Range of that enemy unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
