<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>BASH AND GRAB</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Freebooterz waste no time getting violently stuck 
into anyone unwise enough to try to keep prized loot 
out of their grasping claws.</lore>
    <when>The Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack that targets an 
enemy unit within range of the loot objective, you 
can re‑roll the Wound roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>GRAB AND BASH</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Few warriors in the galaxy fight with greater brutality 
than a Freebooter determined to hang onto his loot.</lore>
    <when>Your Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army (excluding 
Gretchin  units) that is within range of the 
loot objective.</target>
    <effect>Until the start of your next Command phase, 
the Waaagh! is active for your unit, even if you have 
already called a Waaagh! this battle.
Designer’s Note: This means that any abilities that 
are in effect while the Waaagh! is active for your 
army will be in effect for your unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>BOARDIN’ RUSH</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Having cut their gold‑plated fangs storming aboard 
hostile warships, these Freebooterz are good at 
getting stuck straight into the enemy.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to move this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time your 
unit Advances, do not make an Advance roll. Instead, 
until the end of the phase, add 6&quot; to the Move 
characteristic of models in your unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DECK FRAGGERS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Invented by some sadistic Bad Mek, these 
shrapnel‑packed rounds of kustom ammunition 
are excellent for scything down tight‑packed 
enemy infantry.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit targets an Infantry  unit with a 
ranged weapon, that weapon has the [BLAST]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ROLLING LOOT‑HEAP</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Just because an enemy vehicle is still mobile and 
fighting doesn’t stop any suitably arrogant Flash Gitz 
from claiming it as their loot, especially when their 
snazzguns are more than capable of explosively 
backing up that claim.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Flash Gitz  unit from your army that has 
not been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, ranged 
weapons equipped by models in your unit have the 
[ANTI‑VEHICLE 4+]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>KRUMP AND RUN</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>FREEBOOTER KREW</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Freebooterz are unscrupulous pirates through and 
through, always on the look out for new looting 
opportunities and sometimes even willing to forgo a 
good punch up in favour of hauling away their riches.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just after 
an enemy unit falls back.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that was 
within engagement range of that enemy unit at the 
start of the phase and is not within range of one or 
more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of up 
to 6&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
