<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ORKS IS STILL ORKS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Even though they may be armed with the flashiest 
shootas, when enemies stray within arms reach, an 
Orks first and strongest instinct is to use their snazzy 
shoota as a cudgel, and bash their foe to a pulp.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes an attack that targets an 
enemy unit, re‑roll a Wound roll of 1. If that enemy 
unit is within range of an objective marker, you can 
re‑roll the Wound roll instead.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>GET STUCK IN, LADZ!</name>
    <cpCost>2CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>EPIC DEED STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Lashing out with ferocious blows and bellowing loud 
enough to burst eardrums, the biggest Ork present 
persuades his ladz to fight even harder.</lore>
    <when>Your Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army (excluding 
Gretchin  units).</target>
    <effect>Until the start of your next Command phase, 
the Waaagh! is active for your unit, even if you have 
already called a Waaagh! this battle.
Designer’s Note:  This means that any abilities that 
are in effect while the Waaagh! is active for your 
army will be in effect for your unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>HUGE SHOW ‑OFFS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>EPIC DEED STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The pilots of the biggest Orky war machines are 
prone to showing off when the dakka starts flying. 
After all, they have a reputation to uphold.</lore>
    <when>Your Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks Walker  unit (excluding Killa 
Kans ) from your army.</target>
    <effect>Until the start of your next Command phase, 
improve your unit’s Move, Leadership and Objective 
Control characteristics by 1, and each time a model 
in your unit makes an attack, add 1 to the Hit roll.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>LONG, UNCONTROLLED BURSTS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>When facing off against sneaky gitz who like to 
lurk in cover, most Orks believe the most effective 
strategy is to fire off so many bullets and munitions 
that something is bound to hit the target.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, ranged 
weapons equipped by models in your unit have the 
[IGNORES COVER]  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SPESHUL SHELLS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>WARGEAR STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Nothing helps a round punch through armour better 
than stuffing it full of extra propellant.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, each time a 
model in your unit makes a ranged attack that 
targets the closest eligible target within 18&quot;, improve 
the Armour Penetration characteristic of ranged 
weapons equipped by models in your unit by 1.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>CALL DAT DAKKA?</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>MORE DAKKA!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Gun‑crazed mobs of Orks take incoming fire as a 
primal challenge, one that must be answered with an 
even bigger show of dakka.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has shot.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that had one 
or more of its models destroyed as a result of the 
attacking unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can shoot as if it were your 
Shooting phase, but must target only that enemy 
unit when doing so, and can only do so if that enemy 
unit is an eligible target.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
