<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ON DA MOVE</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Speed Freeks live for the thrill of high‑octane warfare, 
rarely letting their feet off the accelerator, even in the 
most furious fighting.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to move this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, your unit is eligible 
to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in which it Fell 
Back or Advanced (unless it used its turbo this turn).</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>MOBILE DAKKASTORM</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>No self‑respecting Speed Freek stops to aim. Instead, 
they fire on the move, concentrating hails of dakka 
on their chosen targets.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase, just after a Speed 
Freeks  or Trukk  unit from your army has shot.</when>
    <target>That Speed Freeks  or Trukk unit.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit hit by one or more of 
those attacks (excluding attacks made with Indirect 
Fire weapons). Until the end of the phase, each time 
a model in a Speed Freeks  or Trukk  unit from your 
army makes an attack that targets that unit, improve 
the Strength characteristic of that attack by 2.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>SPESHUL AMMO</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>WARGEAR STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Though the cost in teef is high, Mek‑crafted speshul 
ammunition always comes in handy when taking on 
big targets.</lore>
    <when>Your Shooting phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that has not 
been selected to shoot this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, ranged weapons 
equipped by models in your unit (excluding 
Torrent weapons) have the [ANTI‑MONSTER 4+]  and 
[ANTI‑VEHICLE 4+]  abilities.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DED KILLY CONSTRUCTION</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Fitted with jagged ploughs, spiked tyres and steel 
bars, Ork vehicles are potent weapons in their 
own right.</lore>
    <when>Your Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Speed Freeks  or Trukk  unit from your 
army that has not been selected to fight this phase.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, melee weapons 
equipped by models in your unit have the [LANCE]  
ability and, if your unit made a Charge move this 
turn, until the end of the phase, add 1 to the Damage 
characteristic of those weapons.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DUST TRAILS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Large formations of Ork vehicles throw up columns 
of dust and clouds of smoke. These combine to 
shroud and obscure them as they thunder across 
the battlefield.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Shooting phase, just after an 
enemy unit has selected its targets.</when>
    <target>One  Orks unit from your army that was 
selected as the target of one or more of the attacking 
unit’s attacks.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the phase, your unit has the 
Benefit of Cover.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>EVASIVE MANOOVA</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>SPEEDWAAAGH!</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>The wiliest Speed Freeks see no shame in running 
away, especially when they can always come back 
and have ’annuva go.</lore>
    <when>End of your opponent’s Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Speed Freeks  or Trukk  unit from your 
army that is not within Engagement Range of one or 
more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Remove your unit from the battlefield and 
place it into Strategic Reserves.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
