<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<stratagems>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DAT’S OURS</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>A few Orks, particularly those of the Blood Axe Clan, 
can resist their destructive urges long enough to 
prioritise the seizing of objectives.</lore>
    <when>Command phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks unit from your army that is within 
Engagement Range of one or more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Until the start of the next Command phase, 
add 1 to the Objective Control characteristic of 
models in your unit.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>FIGHT PROPPA</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Some deviant Blood Axes go so far as to practise 
hand‑to‑hand combat, tailoring fighting styles to 
specific types of enemies.</lore>
    <when>Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Orks Infantry  or Orks Mounted  unit 
from your army that has not been selected to fight 
this phase.</target>
    <effect>Select the [SUSTAINED HITS 1]  or 
[LETHAL HITS]  ability. Until the end of the phase, 
melee weapons equipped by models in your unit 
have the selected  ability.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>TAKTIKAL RETREAT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Blood Axes feel no shame in retreating from a 
fight, particularly if the boss wants someone else 
duffed up.</lore>
    <when>Your Movement phase, just after an Orks  unit 
from your army Falls Back.</when>
    <target>That Orks  unit.</target>
    <effect>Until the end of the turn, your unit is eligible 
to shoot and declare a charge in a turn in which it 
Fell Back.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>KRUNCHIN’ DESCENT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>BATTLE TACTIC STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>With their rocket packs at full throttle, Stormboyz 
plummet to smash into their foes with 
bone‑crushing force.</lore>
    <when>Your Charge phase, just after a Stormboyz  
unit from your army ends a Charge move.</when>
    <target>That Stormboyz  unit.</target>
    <effect>Select one enemy unit within Engagement 
Range of your unit, then roll one D6 for each model 
in your unit that is within Engagement Range of that 
enemy unit: for each 4+, that enemy unit suffers 1 
mortal wound (to a maximum of 6 mortal wounds).</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>ON TO DA NEXT</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Seeing little value in pursuing fleeing foes, Blood Axe 
mobs turn their attention towards the next fight or 
press towards whatever cache of shiny gubbinz the 
boss desires.</lore>
    <when>Your opponent’s Movement phase, just after 
an enemy unit Falls Back.</when>
    <target>One Orks  unit from your army that was 
within Engagement Range of that enemy unit at the 
start of the phase.</target>
    <effect>Your unit can make a Normal move of up 
to 6&quot;.</effect>
  </stratagem>
  <stratagem>
    <name>DED SNEAKY</name>
    <cpCost>1CP</cpCost>
    <type>TAKTIKAL BRIGADE</type>
    <subtype>STRATEGIC PLOY STRATAGEM</subtype>
    <lore>Utilising camouflage, cover or misdirection, these 
Orks slip away to prepare their next ambush, leaving 
their foes staring at thin air.</lore>
    <when>End of your opponent’s Fight phase.</when>
    <target>One Kommandos  or Stormboyz unit from 
your army that is not within Engagement Range of 
one or more enemy units.</target>
    <effect>Remove your unit from the battlefield and 
place it into Strategic Reserves.</effect>
  </stratagem>
</stratagems>
